<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Onepages on PH 290-011: TLBBD</title>
    <link>https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Onepages on PH 290-011: TLBBD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Targeted Learning in Biomedical Big Data!</title>
      <link>https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/00-course_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/00-course_info/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! This is the course website for Targeted Learning in Biomedical Big Data, offered in the Spring 2018 semester at UC Berkeley.
Course Information  Faculty Instructor: Mark van der Laan  Office Hours: Tu 4:00-5:00P in Haviland 108  Graduate Student Instructor: Nima Hejazi  Office Hours: M 2:00-3:00P in Haviland 111  Syllabus (PDF) Course Control Number: 42472 Lectures: TuTh 11:00A-12:30P in Mulford 230 Labs: W 2:00-3:00P in Mulford 230 Mailing list: please subscribe here  Schedule The schedule of video lectures and content is publicly available here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproducible Research with R, git, and GitHub (part 01)</title>
      <link>https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/01-repro_res-part_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/01-repro_res-part_01/</guid>
      <description>Lab 1: Reproducible Research with R, git, GitHub (p.1) Our first lab for Targeted Learning in Biomedical Big Data is a simple introduction to computationally reproducible research with R, git, and GitHub. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the importance of computational reproducibility and set some standards for how these principles apply to the work we&amp;rsquo;ll do in this class.
Resources  Version Control with git (Software Carpentry) R for Reproducible Scientific Analysis (Software Carpentry) Tools for Reproducible Research (Karl Broman) Happy Git and GitHub for the useR (Jenny Bryan)  The above resources provide a mechanism to remedy any deficiencies that may be present in background knowledge on scientific computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproducible Research with R, git, and GitHub (part 2)</title>
      <link>https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/02-repro_res-part_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanderLaan-group.github.io/tlbbd-sp2018/onepage/02-repro_res-part_02/</guid>
      <description> Lab 2: Reproducible Research with R, git, GitHub (p.2) For our second lab, we&amp;rsquo;ll continue our discussion of computationally reproducible research and further explore the simple toolbox at which we&amp;rsquo;ve already started to take a look.
Lab Materials:  GitHub repo (source) nbviewer (static HTML) binder (live notebook)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>